

DAMIAN TCHORZEWSKI

FULLSTACK WEB
DEVELOPER

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node, Python, SQL, PHP, C#, Sass, Git, REST API, Axios, Redux, Jira, Miro, Microsoft, Adobe, Bash, Bootstrap, Express, Webpack, Parcel, Wordpress, PrestaShop, Insomnia, MS360,Slack, Trello, Docker, Ai, Figma,JSON,

SKILLS

Communication, Creativity, Teamwork, Problem Solving, Self-Discipline, Fast Learning, Organization, Precision

CERTIFICATES

FullStack Web Developer 2022/2023 Advanced Python Developer 2024 Advanced PHP/SQL Developer 2024

EDUCATION

Vistula University (currently) Engineer's degree - Computer Science

CONTACT ME.

Phone: (+48) 535 780 277

Email: damiantchorzewski0@gmail.com

LINKS

Linkedin Portfolio GitHub

ABOUT ME

I specialize in building scalable web and mobile applications. I have experience across the entire project lifecycle - from needs analysis to implementation. I am open to new challenges that will allow me to develop skills and bring value to the team.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Czarymary Okulary | 2024

- Creating websites for an optical salon.
- SEO optimization and integration with social media.
- Technical support and training of customers.

AI & MI Developer

Paidwork | 2024

- Create and optimize ML models for NLP analysis and image recognition.
- Implementing AI solutions that increase business value.
- Analyze and improve the performance of ML systems.

Help Desk Technician

Cozmobike | 2021-currently

- Cooperation in the design and development of e-commerce platform for lovers of cycling tourism.
- Ensure compatibility between devices and optimize performance.
- Managing DevOps processes and maintaining code quality.

FullStack Web Developer

GoiT | 09-2022/12-2023

- Creating web applications with an emphasis on e-commerce functionality.Back-end development
- Integration of payment systems, logistics and optimization for mobile users. Testing
- Analyze user traffic data and implement UX improvements.

System Administrator

NaŚcieżce | 2017-2020

- Cooperation in the implementation of a sales and information platform based on WordPress.
- Database management and process optimisation.
- Develop and implement a data security strategy.